from typing import List, Dict


items: Dict[str, Dict[str, List[Dict[str, str]]]] = {

	"Very Common": [
		{"emoji": "ğŸ¬", "name": "Candy"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ«", "name": "Chocolate Bar"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ­", "name": "Lollypop"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸª", "name": "Cookie"}
	],

	"Common": [
		{"emoji": "ğŸ›¼", "name": "Rollerskate"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ¤¿", "name": "Diving Mask"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ", "name": "Volleyball"}
	],

	"Rare": [
		{"emoji": "ğŸ§¸", "name": "Teddybear"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ’µ", "name": "Money"},
		{"emoji": "ğŸ®", "name": "PS5"}
	]

}

questions: Dict[str, List[Dict[str, str]]] = {
	"all": [
		{"question": "What is the present participle form of hunt?", "answer": """Hunting"""},

		{"question": """What is the meaning of the Latin root corpus?""", "answer": """Body"""},

		{"question": """The work of what famous American poet inspired the musical "Cats"?""", "answer": """T.S. Eliot"""},

		{"question": """What is a 12 letter word meaning "having the ability of using both hands with equal skill or ease"?""", "answer": """Ambidextrous"""},

		{"question": """Which of these is a hyperbole, The Horse Is Eating or I Could Eat A Horse?""", "answer": """I Could Eat A Horse"""},

		{"question": """What literary term means a word that has a similar meaning to another word?""", "answer": """Synonym"""},

		{"question": """What word in English means prior to the Civil War?""", "answer": """Antebellum"""},

		{"question": """What is the meaning of the greek prefix poly?""", "answer": """Many"""},

		{"question": """Who said "it is far safer to be feared than loved"?""", "answer": """Niccolo Machiavelli"""},

		{"question": """What is the meaning of the greek prefix geo?""", "answer": """Earth"""},

		{"question": """What is an eight-letter word meaning "one who advocates or practices altruism"?""", "answer": """Altruist"""},

		{"question": """What part of speech is "susceptible", meaning "easily under a specified power or influence"?""", "answer": """Adjective"""},

		{"question": """What is a 6 letter word meaning "a way of approach or entrance; passage"?""", "answer": """Access"""},

		{"question": """What is a 10 letter word meaning "to mix or blend together in a homogeneous body"?""", "answer": """Amalgamate"""},

		{"question": """What is the singular possessive form of "boy"?""", "answer": """Boy's"""},

		{"question": """What is the meaning of the Latin root ultra?""", "answer": """Beyond"""},

		{"question": """In "Mary Poppins", the Banks family lived on what street?""", "answer": """Cherry Tree Lane"""},

		{"question": """What is an 8 letter word meaning "to give credit or authority to"?""", "answer": """Accredit"""},

		{"question": """What punctuation mark ends an imperative sentence?""", "answer": """!"""},

		{"question": """Which word would define the Latin root lingua?""", "answer": """Language"""},

		{"question": """What does "minuscule" mean in latin?""", "answer": """Smaller"""},

		{"question": """What is the meaning of the Latin root sol?""", "answer": """Sun"""},

		{"question": """Cerveza means beer in which language?""", "answer": """Spanish"""},

		{"question": """â€œSame same but differentâ€ is a common phrase meaning â€œsimilarâ€ in which country?""", "answer": """Thailand"""},

		{"question": """You spill a drink on someone at a bar in Rome. You apologise and they reply: â€œTi rifaccio la dentatura.â€ Should you be concerned?""", "answer": """yes"""},

		{"question": """When would you say namaste to someone?""", "answer": """Greeting"""},

		{"question": """Hakuna matata (meaning no worries) was a phrase made popular around the world by the Lion King, but which language is it?""", "answer": """Swahili"""},

		{"question": """In which country do locals use the phrase â€œnot my circus, not my monkeysâ€ when they mean â€œnot my problemâ€?""", "answer": """Poland"""}
	]
}
